Guide to the Pacific Geograpic Society Records, 1927-1940
Department of Special Collections
- World Affairs Session 1938 (Box 7, Folder 99)
Nicholson, Grace Folder 41,55,63
O'Connor, Arthur H. (Australian Natl. Travel Assn.) Folder 7,14,38,48,51,58
O'Melveny, Henry William 1859-(lawyer) Folder 76 (1)
Orcutt, William Warren 1869-(oil exec.) Folder 7,8,57,89
Ortiz, Rubio Pascual 1877-(Mex. politician) Folder 60 (tel.)
Pacific Discovery Day Folder 51,54,55,56
Pacific Geographic Publishing Co. Folder 1
Pacific Magazine Folder 8,58
Palmer, Carl P. (v.p., mg. dir. PGS) Folder 8,52,69
Pan Pacific Progress Folder 57
Pearson, Harry C. (lecturer) Folder 11,61
Peat, Harold R. 1894-(writer, lecturer) Folder 14,27,10,62
Pepperdine, George 1886-(Western Auto Supply of Calif., Pepperdine Foundation, Pepperdine College) Folder 52,64
Philharmonic Auditorium Folder 65,66
Pillsbury, Arthur C. (botanist, photographer?] Folder 27,67,94
Plummer, George T. Folder 19,27
Pollak, Katherine S. Folder 37,76
Pomeroy, Hugh R. 1899-(city planner) Folder 41
Pomona College Folder 68
Pond James B(urton) 1889-(editor, head of lecture bureau) Folder 69
Pottenger, Francis Marion 1869-(physician, surgeon) Folder 7,8,57,82
Potter, Charles Franklin 1861-(attorney) Folder 14,15,55
Prisk, Charles Henry 1875-(editor, publisher) Folder 55,56,63
Prisk, William Frederick 1870-(publisher) Folder 35.57
Putnam, George Palmer 1887-(publisher, author) Folder 71
Read, Humphrey (founder PGS) Folder 57 (m),74,76
Re-organization Folder 74
Rice, George Folder 41,77
Ripley, Robert Le Roy 1893-(artist, author) Folder 21 (m)
Robinson, Edward G. (actor) Folder 19 (1)
Sachse, Richard Folder 82
San Diego Chapter Folder 78,79,80
Sargent, Homer Earle 1875-(elec. engr.) Folder 20,63
Sawders, James Caleb 1894-(lecturer) Folder 20,28,81,87
Sawyer, Ernest Walker (U.S. Sec. of Interior) Folder 41 (1)
Scherer, James Augustin Brown 1870-(educator) Folder 16,21,72 (m)
Scott, James Brown 1866-(lawyer, educator) Folder 7 (1)
Sekku (Boys' Day) Folder 82
Sieg, Lee Paul 1879-(univ. pres.) Folder 7 (1)
Siemel, Sasha Alejandro Folder 14,15,18
Simpson, Anita Folder 13,19,20,27
Smith, George Leslie 1873-(auditorium mgr.) Folder 66
Smith, Nina Folder 14, 27
Spaulding, Frank Ellsworth 1866-(educator) Folder 13
Spencer, M(atthew) Lyle 1881 (univ. dean) Folder 8 (1)
Sproul, Robert Gordon 1891-(pres. U.C.) Folder 7,8,63
Stacy-Judd, Robert Benjamin 1884-(architect) Folder 88
Starbuck, Edwin Diller 1866-(univ. Prof.) Folder 41,76
Stefansson, Vilhjamur 1879-(artic explorer) Folder 19,27
Stein, Jan J. (attorney) Folder 15,25
Stevenson, Marcia Jacobs 1875-(lecturer) Folder 10,14,22,94
Swaffield, Roland G. 1884-(attorney) Folder 34,36
Taussig, Joseph Knefler 1877 (naval officer) Folder 7 (1)
Tejada Sorzano, Jose Luis 1881-1938 (pres. Bolivia) Folder 8
Terriss, Tom Folder 52,91
Terwilliger, Ivan M. Folder 57
Thomas, Lowell 1892-(author,lecturer) Folder 62 (m), 87
Truman, Herbert Frederic (lecture Mgr.) Folder 22 (1)
Walters, Theodore Augustus (asst. sec. Interior) Folder 23 (1)
Ware, Carolyn E. Folder 69,94
Wells, (Grant) Carveth 1887-(explorer, author) Folder 95
Wilbur Ray Lyman Folder 7 (1)
Wilson, Elmer Folder 25,98
Winter, Alice Ames 1865-(author) Folder 8,82
Young, Archibald B. Folder 55,63
Young, George Gilray 1876-(newspaper publisher) Folder 7 (1)